http://iwasaki-images.com/index.php?main_page=privacy&zenid=615a846ff156c91aa93718300c7882f6

Warning:
session_start() [function.session-start]: Cannot send session cache limiter - headers already sent (output started at /home/49/93/7009349/web/index.php:1) in /home/49/93/7009349/web/includes/functions/sessions.php on line 111
videocelebs.net
Home |
Log In
Email:
Password:
Shipping & ReturnsPrivacy NoticeConditions of UseContact UsNewsletter UnsubscribeMedia Archives  Our Clients List
Who's Online
There currently are 4 guests online.
Home :: Privacy Notice
Privacy Notice
Effective 8/1/2005
Our Commitment To Privacy
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide
this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you
can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this
notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point
where personally identifiable information may be requested.
The Information We Collect:
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the IWASAKI IMAGES OF AMERICA website.
On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register
to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages
are:
On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example,
if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will
need to submit the recipient's address. In this circumstance, the types of personal
information collected are:
The Way We Use Information:
We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only
to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties
except to the extent necessary to complete that order.
We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order
only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information
with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.
We offer gift-cards by which you can personalize a product you order for another
person. Information you provide to us to create a gift-card is only used for
that purpose, and it is only disclosed to the person receiving the gift.
We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses
are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.
You can register with our website if you would like to receive our catalog
as well as updates on our new products and services. Information you submit
on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration
form.
We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website
and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X
number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number
of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would
not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.
Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided
to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing
you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.
Our Commitment To Data Security:
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct
use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and
managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that
reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we
actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract
anyone under 13.
How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information:
You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect
online and maintain by logging in and clicking on my account in the above menu. We use
this procedure to better safeguard your information.
How To Contact Us:
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an
email at sales@iwasaki-images.com.
| Home |
Your IP Address is:
72.182.10.230
Serving User :
2649293 Since 04/18/2005
Copyright © 2005 IWASAKI IMAGES OF AMERICAPowered by AAA Computer Services Net.Please Report Errors Here !
